[Music]
[Applause]
no way
the kids are having a Sleetover tonight
you don't have to ruin it by
being drunk off your ass besides we need
to go out to buy Manic's axe body spray
since we got the wrong one what are you
saying
[ __ ] Edward is way better than Jacob
that's why Bella picked him
well I'm saying she made a mistake Jacob
is clearly the better boyfriend
than that sparkling pretty boy [ __ ]
boyfriend
they were never even dating to begin
with doesn't matter what you think you
God dang [ __ ]
because Edward won either way you're
just salty
how dare you you dare disrespect me in
my own home
get the hell off me Sonic you better let
go of your sister right now
that is enough what in the world has
gotten into you kids
stop said stop it you fat [ __ ]
we just got done watching twilight
breaking dawn
it was his first time and now he won't
quit saying Jacob is better than Edward
only because he is mom
Uncle Chuck you two are on team Jacob
right
tell her she's wrong oh
you don't know how to link topic or
toyota
I'm almost sold so primero don't
know if it's reformatter the whatever to
accept intense
sparking off of sharing things
you sure you got everything pumpkin i
don't mind heading back to the house if
you need something
oh daddy you're such a worry what for
the last time yes
oh you know me sugar just got to look
out for my girl
daddy you don't need to worry it's just
a slumber party at my friend's house
like come on I mean really what's the
worst that could happen
i don't like that tone young lady you
are my girl
aren't you say it say it loud and clean
yeah here I am I'm your precious baby
girl daddy
that's it say it for daddy you dirty
[ __ ]
little [ __ ] [ __ ]
[Music]
i I'm gonna head out if you need
anything just give me a call
so this is the place where we're going
to have the slumber party my bitch's
house
how sad it's so small I bet it only cost
89 trillion dollars
but I guess that's how it goes
thankfully I'm not a judging person
i simply cannot wait to see my bitch's
face like when he sees
that I brought him the limited edition
drink a baja blast from taco Bell
he'll be so excited I bet he'll even
suck my balls
or should I say suck my burrito huh
hey [ __ ] open the door and tuck on my
penis
not showing up I see I guess you like
playing hard to get
that's fine by me should I just blow
down the door with nothing but my
[ __ ] piss again
wow the way is that a blast from taco
Bell
can I have one no way piss off
go get your own knees up for me and my
beak
oh God damn it look what you've done you
broke my concentration
and made me pee in my buja blush
well at least now I know which one my
[ __ ] is getting
Knuckles Bartleby you're just in time me
and my bro were just getting done
preparing snacks for tonight's Sleetover
how are you ready for a night with just
the guys
you bet and look I brought you a little
surprise
a wonderful guy blast from taco Bell
oh bartelby you treat me so well
if there's one thing that I can't say
for certainty is that i
Sonic the Hedgehog really love the
limited edition drink aha blast from
taco Bell
[ __ ] who are you talking to let's go
upstairs to my room
me and Manic rented this really kick-ass
game from blockbuster
okay
hey Mindy what do you wanna do first the
other girls didn't arrive yet
but I'm sure we can't still find ways to
have fun
Sonia what is going on here I thought
you invited 12 other girls
where is everyone you're the only one
who showed up so far
I'm sure they'll get here eventually but
I'm seven hours late
i got an idea let's facetime everyone
and see what's going on
maybe they're just stuck in traffic
somewhere
we'll try calling sari first since she
seemed most excited and [ __ ]
why howdy there sonja how are you doing
this evening sorry I took so long to
answer your call
i was just busy sucking paws balls but i
mean I was just busy helping my
boyfriend
jaya in the farm you know bundling hay
and what not
i definitely wasn't cheating on him with
his pr
or anything ha ha
where the hell are you [ __ ] Cyrus the
reason we called you was to figure
out if you're still on for the Sleetover
tonight
that was tonight holy moly I forgot
entirely about that no
I'm not coming over i'll try and make it
up to you next time by bringing my
delicious home down macaroni salad
it's a real treat how's it hanging
well besides all of these guys balls
over here at the local strike club haha
Mindy why are you at the strip mall when
you've been planning the slumber party
for weeks
more importantly why didn't you take me
with you
[Music]
um Cyrus who's that behind you
uh what oh you must have seen Jared
we just got done having steamy sex out
in the pasture
no I'm I'm pretty sure that was jars
[Music]
paul
Cyrus paw you in there thought you were
being real sneaky going out to the barn
behind my back don't you
well I'm not stupid and no luck can
guard you against my rage
come on out and get yours paw I told you
what would happen if I caught
you [ __ ] my girl again I'm gonna blow
your brains out
i think I'm gonna get going you girls
have fun now yeah here
Cyrus shut that [ __ ] camera off cause
I'm gonna rape your ass
so long you too I gotta get back to work
if I stay on this vid too long the
police will find out my location
later [ __ ]
okay kids we're leaving for the store
remember to keep all the doors locked up
and don't forget to go to bed at nine if
it gets too cold
turn up the thermostat in the hall
do you think the kids will be okay by
themselves
maybe one of us should stay back just in
case
it's finesses the kids are old enough to
take care of themselves
and they see this Bartleby is so strong
i can lift a monster to quick use these
boot checks
you made a huge mistake challenging
Knuckles the cool Echidna to a game of
twister
everybody knows I'm the king when it
comes to board games
yet well you're gonna see who's really
the king of twister tonight
let's make a bet then [ __ ] loser owes
the other one five bucks
Manic left hand green
[Music]
sorry Knux I should have told you I ate a
spicy bean and cheese burrito this
morning haha
haha you should warn the guy before you
go and do stuff
like that that [ __ ] was stinky
is this really what poor people do at
Sleetovers well
i guess it is on the guy the type
printed off from the poor person's
Wikipedia page
but they're doing everything out of
order this is all just so confusing to
me
hey [ __ ] what time are we going to have
the pillow fight
a pillow fight um I don't think we were
planning on having a pillow fight
my bro and I only have a couple pillows
so it wouldn't be possible since there's
four of us
but my guide says poor people do that
well
pillow fights are more of a girl's thing
i see so only poor females participate
in
pillow fights I was really looking
forward to that too
[ __ ] can you tell me where the bathroom
in your house is
so that I may go poop
moments like this where I can plainly
see that I am different from everybody
else
I'm different from everybody I'm weird
all because I'm the richest man on earth
it's not like it's anything new either
from the very beginning I have suffered
under this burden
hey Bartleby you know today is my
birthday
the rest of the class are coming over to
my place after school
for a huge Sleetover there's going to be
cake and ice cream too
and solar sticks with peanut butter we
got big muscles and I also hear you're
the richest
kid in school I think that's kinda cool
do you want to come to my Sleetover I’ve
got an extra invitation
dude what the hell are you doing why
would you give an invite to Bobby
everybody knows he's the weird kid he's
different from the rest of us
that's right I hear his family is so
rich that he's tapped threatened to buy
the entire school
if any of the teachers even dare to give
Bartleby anything lower than an a-plus
if I were you i'd be scared to be
friends with someone who has that much
power
you know what you guys are right
Bartleby you're not invited to my
Sleetover anymore
you're a freak a monster
come one let's go see if they're serving
chicken nuggets in the cafeteria today
oh my God barnabas
[Music]
i finally know why I can't get an answer
i finally know
me
[Music]
is
can anybody make me
[Music]
oh sorry [ __ ] I didn't know you are out
here
what do you want Bartleby my beautiful
lover I heard you singing all the way
from down the hall
tell me honestly are you not having fun
at my Sleetover
I'm so sorry if it's not to your
satisfaction
you don't have to apologize my [ __ ]
it's not your fault your Sleeter sucks
big sweaty balls
you know I just struggle to fit in with
you poor people and your poor people
activities
oh my God peeing in poor people's
bathrooms is so boring
there's not even a roller coaster or a
butler to give you a warm towel and a
small bottle of soap after you're done
oh would you look at the time it's
almost 9 p.m
didn't your mom say it's lights off at
nine we should hurry to bed
where do I [ __ ] go I don't have a key
for the door
i don't know try punching that [ __ ] ha
ha ha it worked
yeah I just don't know why edmund is
following you around like that
maybe he's [ __ ] gay I think he's
peter's younger brother
i know but he could still be homosexual
[Music]
Sonic are you [ __ ] [ __ ] dear God
what is wrong with you
we were just playing the chronicles of
narnia for the Playstation 2.
yeah bro have you lost your marbles this
game doesn't even ought to save
but bro it's nine o'clock and mama said
we all have to be in bed by nine
your mom isn't even here she want out
remember we have two Knux our mom
always says good kids go to bed on time
Manic you can be such a square sometimes
you know that
good night Knuckles good night bart
libby
I'm sorry you have to Sleet on the floor
babe there's just not enough space in
the bunk bed for all four of us
and well with me being the thick little
boy that I am I take up a whole bed
myself
don't worry about it my bitch I wouldn't
be caught dead Sleeting in a poor
person's bed anyway
I'm just fine and dandy Sleeting in my
solid gold Sleeting bag
that cost 906 trillion dollars
night bro I guess i'll see you in the
morning
now hold on a Mobius minute bro aren't
you forgetting something
you know that special thing the two of
us do just before bed every night
[Music]
well what are you waiting for bring it
on in here my special baby bro
aha what is it little bro you look like
you're thinking about something really
hard
it's nothing big bro nothing at all I'm
just really happy right now
it's just been so long since mom let us
have a Sleetover you know
i had fun today
okay okay that's enough row quit
breathing down my neck it tickles
oh come on bro can't I keep my arms
around you for just a little bit longer
[Music]
KKnux Knuckles hey hey Knuckles are you
awake
Manic what do you want can't you see
it's almost one in the morning
i was just having a really awesome dream
where I was drinking root beer and
eating cookies
I'm hungry let's go downstairs and sneak
some food out of the fridge
no I want to go back to Sleet come on
Knux my mom just bought some macaroni
i'll make you some of my world famous
Manic and cheese
what the [ __ ] is Manic ‘n cheese
it's just kraft macaroni and cheese but
my bro thinks his is special
because he adds green food coloring i
call it Manic ‘n cheese because
it's green like me Manic just go back to
bed we're trying to Sleet
up bro where did you go
what are you doing my bro yo everybody
you're just in time for some of my world
famous Manic ‘n cheese
how about you all pull up the seat I'm
about to rock your world with this
cheesy [ __ ]
all that's left for me to do is to add
the secret ingredient
okay bro go easy on the green food color
ring you know how much that [ __ ] costs
if you run out mom's gone a beepist
but bitch it's just a tiny bottle of
food coloring
i mean how much could it cost fifty six
thousand dollars
open your mouth bitch here comes the
chewy shoot rain
[Applause]
Sonia it looks like your mom and uncle
are home
but Mindy that doesn't really look like
my mom's car
yo Bobby Moonbeam you made sure to scope
this place out before
right you sure there's nobody inside I'm
not about to be caught and spend four
more years in prison
I’ve done my I'm positive time
this house sketch I saw the family carl
leave a couple hours ago
the place is empty big brother
are you sure you want to do this you
have always told me stealing is wrong
what happened to you it's like ever
since you met Bobby Moonbeam
you've changed Cindy you know mom and
ted have the coronavirus
because they were anti-massacres if we
don't find a way to get money
we'll never be able to afford their
vaccines and hospital bills
there are plenty of other ways to get
money take me
back to the strip club and i'll show you
i make six dollars a day
Cindy I told you six dollars is nothing
just mods hospital bills alone are eight
thousand bucks
sorry to interrupt your little solid
story but are we going to get down to
business or
what sorry Bobby Moonbeam I got
distracted
what's the plan I will tell you the plan
but first the screen
has got to pass some gas out of his ass
okay let's get out of the car i'll tell
you the plan when we get up by the
driveway
okay here is the plan we're going to get
that door open
and when you do the three of us rush in
and steal [ __ ]
if we come across any live forms let me
know immediately so I can tell that
Bobby Moonbeam wants to be out there in
10 minutes or less
don't worry Bobby we'll be in and out of
there before anybody
even know what happened let's get going
butternuts the door is locked body
keep your eyes open for unlickers I'm
going to use my pistol to blow the log
no
what's that do you got a better idea
we shall use my alien green it at least
a special frequency so high
that it cannot be picked up by
earthlings
it is said that man advantage hold
himself took one of these models into
the final battle against Doctor Robotnik
and that he used it to blow robotics
clothes clean
Bobby why are you the only one I ever
hear that story from
I'm starting to think you make [ __ ] up
as you go along
[Music]
hey does anyone hear that loud ringing
sound I think it's coming from outside
what do you think it is some kind of
weird emergency alarm
it's not an alarm you idiot it's an
alien ray from Mobius
but how I thought all alien rays were
lost when Mobius fell
they were until today that is somehow
one ended up in this very neighborhood
perhaps it's a mobian who came looking
for revenge since the Hedgehog royal
family failed them
you guys there's a group of weirdos out
front I think someone's trying to break
in
Bartleby I'm frightened what do we do
everyone scatter it's every man for
himself
look rodney alien food
that's not alien food body moon bean I'm
pretty sure that it's just mac and
cheese with green food coloring poured
on top
it's what you're seeing is true then it
must mean there are life forms somewhere
in the house let's split up and find
them
Cindy you're going stairs and check out
there rodNick
you stay in the kitchen and have a look
around
while you do that I'm going to take a
big [ __ ] double the toilet
good luck bro if you need anything just
call
i'll be right there
yo Manic what are we going to do there's
no way we can make to the front door
like this I don't know I got the police
on the phone right now maybe we should
try the window
good idea [ __ ] let's do it to it
Knuckles watch out for the
oh no I'm stuck Knuckles pull me hurry
up
i can't get my fat ass through the
window God why do I have to be related
to Sonic the Hedgehog
just hold tight man I got you
that was a warning shot red boy now get
the foot out of here unless
you want me to pop a cap in your butt
now that we're alone it's time
no please don't kill me i'll do anything
tell you who said anything about killing
you
I'm just gonna [ __ ] you [ __ ]
you know what I wanna enjoy this you
stay right here
I'm going out front and i'll meet you
outside so you can suck my balls
see you in a moment babe
this is the police put your hands up
you're under arrest [ __ ]
[Applause]
Bartleby I'm scared he has a gun what
are we going to do
hurry up and shut that hole under your
nose if you don't make a sound he won't
find us
don't think I didn't hear that I know
there's someone hiding behind
the shower curtain coming out right now
or else I'm going to rip your balls off
with my teeth
God damn it [ __ ] you and your
planet-sized butt cheeks
i don't guess screams of the innocent
perhaps I was wrong and there's nobody
after all
wow Bartleby you caught every single
one of the bullets in your bare hands
how did you manage to do that haha we've
been over this remember I'm even faster
than you [ __ ]
yes even faster than Sonic the Hedgehog
himself
who are you what the hell are you
choking me with [ __ ]
these are my panties I hope you don't
mind that they're covered in my [ __ ]
pee
Sonia hurry grab the hammer that i
shoved up my big smelly ass five minutes
ago
break this bitch's legs
[Music]
i will take that kind of your hands
hurry up and kill her Mindy
I'm going to call the police no Sonia
I'm going to enjoy this
i want her death to be slow and painful
[Music]
i think somebody was hiding behind the
shower curtain wall
i was cooking go find your brother we're
gonna make like a bunch of bananas
and peel out what the hell is going on
here
Cindy get up get a piece of the [ __ ]
you killed her
you [ __ ] killed her didn't you I’ve
heard stories about you Bobby Moonbeam
they say you're the most evil alien
criminal in the galaxy
but also one of the most cowardly and
most stupid
hi Bartleby Montclair of Dresden the
richest and sexiest man on earth
will make you pay for ruining my bitch's
special Sleetover
prepare yourself you little green major
boy
[ __ ] if I had known that this was the
house of Bartleby's personal [ __ ]
Sonic they catch you up I would never
have come here
i didn't spill anything yet if you let
me go I promise don't even never come
back
please please forgive me you want
forgiveness
find religion
hey Bartleby do you know what's funny
in a way
it seems you did get your pillow fight
after all
hey you're right it looks like I did and
i
even had fun too
Bobby Moonbeam you are under arrest for
136 counts of galactic murder
and home invasion your friend rodNick
here told us everything
so don't even try running away you
naughty little alien boy
hey kids where are you back
and look whoever broke pisa
hey [ __ ] now that this mess is over
with how about we start this Sleetover
for realest
yeah I think that sounds quite nice then
what's the holdup
let's go have a hot and ready ham and
pineapple pizza
for only five dollars from little
and caesars building a brighter light
when no one
[Music]
all knows we'll run away
into the fields of gold where dreams
[Music]
you